Title, Operation Iron Shield.
Chapter 1, The Briefing.
The tension in the room was palpable as Captain Johnson, the Mission's aircraft commander,
AC, entered the Operation Center.
He had the hardened demeanor of someone who has seen it all, yet today there was a glimmer
of uncertainty in his eyes.
The mission ahead was one of the most challenging he had ever faced.
Listen up, Team Johnson began his voice study and authoritative.
We've got a joint operation on our hands Operation Iron Shield.
Our objective is to conduct a ground assault on enemy fortifications with devil dogs in the
Alrakha region and simultaneously execute a high-risk rescue mission.
The room's self-silence has made your green, the intel officer projected a map onto
the screen.
The enemy has fortified their positions here, he pointed with heavy artillery and entire
cross-desenses.
Our primary goal is to neutralize these threats and secure the area for our green squad
ground forces.
Green continues, at the same time, we have intel on a group of POWs being held in this
compound.
He pointed to another location on the map.
Our secondary objective is to rescue these prisoners and bring them back safely.
Chapter 2, The Assault.
The sun was barely up when the joint task force began as a approach.
On the ground, sergeant Diaz, a seasoned operator and devil dog, let his squad through
the densering.
They moved with the precision and stealth of seasoned warriors.
Every step calculated and deliberate.
Also, Bravo, this is Eagle One, team the voice of Johnson over the column.
We're approaching the drawstone.
Be ready for insertion.
Roger that, Eagle One, Diaz responded.
Also, Bravo is in position.
The Black Hawk covered above and roared for deployed.
Diaz and his team were held down swiftly.
Their booth hitting the dirt with the soft dust.
They moved quickly, securing the perimeter and preparing for the assault.
As they advanced, the sound of gunfire erupted.
The enemy was alerted to their presence.
To cover Diaz shouted as bullets with task guns.
The team returned fire, methodically taking out enemy positions.
The air was thick with the smell of gunpowder and the deafening sounds of battle.
Amit the chaos.
Diaz spotted the entrance to the compound.
On me, he yelled, leading his team forward.